Guide to the Ronald Spector papers, 1968-2019 MS2396
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Course Materials, 1989-2013; undated; Series 2
  - Gradebooks, undated; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Haifa University Course & Student Records, undated; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - HH104: American Naval History in a Global Context, 2010; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - HH4360 Naval Academy, 2010; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - History 101.15, 2004; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - History 101.16, 2004; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - History 101.17, Fall, 2002; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - History 101.18, Fall, 2008; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - History 126, Spring, 1997; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - History 126, Spring, 2004; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - History 126, 2006; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - History 126, Spring, 2009; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - History 126, Fall, 2010; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - History 129, Fall, 2001; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - History/Honors 175, Fall, 1996; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - History 182, Fall, 2006; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - History 182w, Spring, 2008; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - History 199, 2005; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - History 228, Spring, 2005; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - History 229, Summer, 1992; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - History 229, Spring, 2003; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - History 229, Spring, 2008; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - History 230 - Ed Raines, 1994; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - History 230, Summer, 1991; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - History 230, Summer, 1996; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - History 230, Fall, 2001; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - History 230, Summer, 2002; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - History 230, 2002; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - History 230, Fall, 2003; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - History 230, 2004; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - History 230, 2005; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - History 230 Transparencies, 2007-2008; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - History 230, Fall, 2010; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - History 657 - Vietnam Seminar, 1989; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Honors 142, 1993; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Hot Wars in the Cold War - History 223, Spring, 2008; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Presentation Materials, 2005; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Transparencies, 2002; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - New Vietnam Stuff, undated; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Princeton, 1990; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Reinventing the Sailor, undated; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Strat, 2012; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 230 Syllabus (Tom's and Mine), 2006; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Remembering America's Wars in Asia, 1995; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan, 2011; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam, 2013; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Tenth Naval History Symposium, 1991; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Vietnam Discussion, 1995; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam Honors 175, 1996; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - War & Society, 1992; MS2396 Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Professional Activity, 1968-2014; undated; Series 3
  Most of this series is open for research. One box has been restricted for 20 years and will be available to review in 2039.
  - 1898, 1998; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "Eagle" Letters [1/3], 1983-1996; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - "Eagle" Letters [2/3], 1984-1996; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - "Eagle" Letters [3/3], 1985-1996; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1973 Nuclear Alert, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - After Hiroshima: Allied Military Occupation and the Fate of Japan's Empire, 1945-1947, 2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - After Tet - Letters From Readers, 1996; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Air Power Proposal, 1993; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Antiques Info, Auction Receipts, and Price Lists, etc. [1/2], 1982-1996; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Antiques Info, Auction Receipts, and Price Lists, etc. [2/2], 1971-1988; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Appraisals from Feng Antiques, 1998; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Army War College, 2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - At War At Sea, 1994; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Atta Boy!, 1991-2000; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Australia, 2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Beverly Video, Victoria Costello, 1996; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Bloch, "Psychological Adjustment of Normal People", 1970; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Bogazici, 1999; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Bogazici Parea, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Book Correspondence, 1985-1990; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Brazinsky, 2007; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - British Studies, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Canned Lectures, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Cold War Docs, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Combat Refusals Research, 1969; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Constructions of Masculinity, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Counter-Insurgency, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Crete, 1989-1998; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Cultural Identity, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - DAHAC, 2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - D-Day Museum, 2001; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Drugs Research, 1969-1971; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Extras, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fragging Research, 1971-1976; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - GW Appointment, 1990; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Harvard - Sino Japanese War, 2001; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - History and Memory, 2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Hornet/Mustin Reunion, 2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Information, 2002; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Inventories/Appraisals, 1983-1998; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Japan Found, 2002; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Joint Conference of the Association for Asia Studies & International Convention of Asia Scholars, 2011; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - KCTS, 2001; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - KEIO Courses, 2000-2001; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - KEIO Paper, 1998; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Leah's Outline (Translations Pending), undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Limits of Technology, 1997; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Map, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - MHQ, 1988; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Military Documents, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Military Schools Paper, 1995 March 2; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Lecture Materials, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Monash University, 1994; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Montana Talk, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - National Defense University, 1996; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Naval Institute Letter, 1995; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Naval Review, 1992; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Near East South Asia (NESA) Executive Seminar, 2007; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Oakland Army Depot, 1998; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Occupation Lecture with Transparencies, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Oxford, 1991-1999; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Pacification and Civilian Attitudes Research, 1969; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Permissions Received, 1999; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Phoenix Research, 1969-1978; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Photos, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Prelude to World War II, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Professors of War Reviews, 1977-1979; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Project 100,000 Research, 1968-1971; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Publicity, 2002; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Published Works, 1972-2014; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 25)
  - R/TTS, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Race Research, 1968-1969; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ristumeikan University, 1998; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - RITS Courses, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sabbatical, 1998-2001; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - SF 171, 1992; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Smithsonian, 2002-2003; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Society for Historians of American Foreign Relations Annual Meeting, 2007; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Spector - Annual Faculty Report, 1992-2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Spector - Report on Sabbatical Leave, 1994; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Spector - Resume, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Speech, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Speedy Express Research, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The Second World War According to Spector - Intelligence, 2003-2005; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - The Second World War According to Spector - The Operational Dimension, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - The United States and East Asia: From the Opium Trade to Pearl Harbor, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Time/Life, 2001; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Vermon CSE/SAIS Meeting, 2003; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam - "What Students Need to Know", undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Vietnam & Other Correspondence, undated; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Vietnam Research, 1991; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Vincent Orange, 1992-1993; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Williamsburg/VVA Meeting, 2000; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - WWII Manuscript Feedback [1/2], 1975-1984; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - WWII Manuscript Feedback [2/2], 1976-1984; MS2396 Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)